Finding Aid for Prentiss Marsh Brown Papers 1902-1973
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Legislative files 1933-1942
  - Legislative files (Bills arranged by Congress, Session, and Number)
    - 75th Congress, 3rd Session
      - S. 4021, U.S. Mail Train Service (Box 7)
      - S. 4123, Homer P. Cota (Box 7)
    - 76th Congress, lst Session
      - S. 1379, Mackinac Straits Bridge, 2 folders (Box 7)
      - S. 1381, Charles A. Goetz (Box 7)
      - S. 1383, Restriction of Alien Laborers (Box 7)
      - S. 1384, Egon Karl Freherr von Mauchonheim (Box 7)
      - S. 1385, Barkman Lumber Co (Box 7)
      - S. 1387, Ida May Lennon (Box 7)
      - S. 1390, Martha Bertha Rapin (Box 7)
      - S. 1391, Delta Teachout (Box 7)
      - S. 1714, Coast Guard Station at Keweenaw Peninsula (Box 7)
      - S. 2045, Bank Examining Bill (special) (Box 7)
      - S. 2275, Floyd M. Dunscomb (Box 7)
      - S. 2276, R.G. Schreck Lumber Co (Box 7)
      - S. 2277, Nicholas Contopoulos (Box 7)
      - S. 2279, Grosse Ile Airport (Box 7)
      - S. 2281, Viola J. Buchanan (Box 7)
      - S. 2286, Detroit Arsenal Grounds Bill (Box 7)
      - S. 2287, Relief of Natives of India (Box 7)
      - S. 2927, Forest Restoration (Box 7)
      - S. 2951, Joseph Henry Hudson (Box 7)
      - S. 2969, Louise Thorne (Box 7)
    - 76th Congress, 2nd Session
      - H.J. Resolution 306: Neutrality Act Amendment (Box 7)
      - S. 3316, Use of War Department equipment at American Legion Convention (Box 7)
    - 76th Congress, 3rd Session
      - H.J. Resolution 407, Trade Agreements Amendment (Box 7)
      - H.J. Resolution 544, Relief Appropriation Bill Amendment (Box 7)
      - H.R. 6324, Exceptions from Walter-Logan Bill (Box 7)
      - S. 1164, Donald A. Jones (Box 7)
      - S. 1970, Labor Practices Bill Amendment (Box 7)
      - S. 2471, Hatch Bill Amendment
        - General, 7 folders (Box 7)
        - Testimony (Box 8)
        - Roll Call (Box 8)
      - S. 3441, Naturalization of Ilhan New (Box 8)
      - S. 3591, Loans to Finland (Box 8)
      - S. 3708, National Firearms Act (Box 8)
      - S. 3709, Internal Revenue Code Amendment (Box 8)
      - S. 3737, Patrick O'Connor (Box 8)
      - S. 3932, Frank and Paulina Rublein (Box 8)
      - S. 3934, Soo Bridge (Box 8)
      - S. 3985, Securities Act of 1933 Amendment (Box 8)
      - S. 4398, John L. Lavan (Box 8)
    - 77th Congress, lst Session
      - S. Resolution 124, Food for Small Democracies (Box 8)
      - S. 854, Richard Bowers (Box 8)
      - S. 899, Earnest A. McNabb (Box 8)
      - S. 909, Cecile M. Franking (Box 8)
      - S. 910, Development of Mineral Resources, Allegan County (Box 8)
      - S. 956, St. Ignace Fish Hatchery (Box 8)
      - S. 957/58 ,Glen Robinson (Box 8)
      - S. 1010, Marine Training Base, Detroit (Box 8)
      - S. 1130, Anna River Fish Hatchery (Box 8)
      - S. 1131, Porcupine Mountains Forest Bill, 5 folders (Box 8)
      - S. 1162, Coast Guard Cutter for Mackinac Straits (Box 8)
      - S. 1163, Katherine Caulley (Box 8)
      - S. 1166, Daniel Steele (Box 8)
      - S. 1167, Herbert Therrien Bill (Box 8)
      - S. 1168, Elsie Frayer (Box 8)
      - S. 1169, Minas Kirillidis (Box 8)
      - S. 1170, Dionis Moldowan (Box 8)
      - S. 1172, Alien Citizenship (Box 8)
      - S. 1173, Alien Veterans Bill (Box 8)
      - S. 1174, Chippewa Indians Bill (Box 8)
      - S. 1175, Ruth Iola Goulette Pridham, 3 folders (Box 8)
      - S. 1176, Jacob Betzer (Box 8)
      - S. 1177, William F. Pack (Box 8)
      - S. 1214, John C. Shaw (Box 8)
      - S. 1215, Fish Hatchery, Keweenaw Peninsula (Box 8)
      - S. 1217, Herbert James Pike (Box 8)
      - S. 1218 R.P, Helm (Box 8)
      - S. 1230, Hospital Construction Act of 1941 (Box 8)
      - S. 1248/4, Isle Royale Bills (Box 8)
      - S. 1408, Luedtke Engineering Co (Box 8)
      - S. 1438, Extending authority of Reconstruction Finance Corporation (Box 9)
      - S. 1448, Canadian and British Vessels to transport iron ore between U.S. ports during 1941 (Box 9)
      - S. 1601, Coast Guard Light Station, Au Sable (Box 9)
      - S. 1603, Banking Facilities at Military Preservations (Box 9)
      - S. 1617, Employment Stabilization (Box 9)
      - S. 2039, National Banking Association (Box 9)
      - S. 2106, St. Mary's River Survey for facilitating light craft navigation (Box 9)
      - S. 2107, Harriet Goodman (Box 9)
      - S. 2131, Charlip Painting and Decorating Company (Box 9)
      - H.R. 5000, Ferd W. Neile (Box 9)
      - H.R. 5990, Emergency Price Control Act (Box 9)
      - S. J. Resolution 161, Price Bill (Box 9)
      - S. 1216, Henry Gabriel (Box 9)
      - S. 2108, Detroit Post Office Clerks (Box 9)
      - S. 2204, Canadian ships to transport iron ore on the Great Lakes during 1942 (Box 9)
      - S. 2285, Admiral Hart (Box 9)
      - S. 2400, Overtime payments to employees under government contract (Box 9)
      - S. 2472, Naming of Soo Locks, 2 folders (Box 9)
      - S. 2485, R.F.C. Subsidy Bill (Box 9)
      - S. 2923, Tivoli Brewing Company (Box 9)
  - Patronage
    - Circuit Court of Appeals Judgeship 1938-July 1941, 5 folders (Box 9)
    - Eastern District of Michigan Judgeship
      - Support for Arthur Koscinski, 5 folders (Box 9)
      - Support for miscellaneous candidates, 3 folders (Box 9)
    - Assistant U.S. Attorney for the Upper Peninsula 1937-February 1940, 6 folders (Box 9)
    - Assistant U.S. Attorney for Detroit 1938 (Box 9)
    - Assistant U.S. Attorney for Bay City 1938-1941 (Box 9)
    - Military Academy Appointments (Charles K. Leech) (Box 10)
    - Military Academy Appointment (miscellaneous) (Box 10)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Letters of thanks received for votes on bills and other legislative favors, 7 folders (Box 10)
    - Congressional Office Expenditures (Box 10)
- Speeches, articles, etc 1911, 1937-1967, 3 linear feet
  The Speeches Articles, etc. series (3 linear ft.; 1911 and 1937-1967) consists mainly of speeches and background material used in the preparation of speeches. The speeches have been arranged chronologically by date on which the speech was first presented. Each folder usually contains a copy of the speech, earlier drafts, and correspondence relating to the presentation of the address, including feedback from his listeners and requests for copies. The speeches are primarily in the period of 1937 to 1943, but there are also later addresses. The earliest item in this series is an address which apparently Brown gave at his commencement from Albion College in 1911.
  - Articles
    - "Stop Tax-Exempt Securities?" Rotarian, February 1941 (Box 10)
    - "Should We Pay As We Go?" Modern Industry Magazine, March 15, 1941 (Box 10)
    - "Michigan, My Michigan" Pathfinder Magazine, undated (Box 10)
  - News releases and related material
    - Various, 3 folders (Box 10)
  - Speeches: chronological file
    - Fragments and undated (Box 10)
    - Commencement Address, Albion College, entitled, "The Student's Debt to the Laboring Man" circa 1911 (Box 10)
    - Democratic State Convention February 20, 1937 (Box 10)
    - Supreme Court Reorganization, Mutual Broadcasting System March 2, 1937 (Box 10)
    - Commencement Day Address, Albion College June 7, 1937 (Box 10)
    - Bunker Hill Celebration and Banquet, Boston Mass. June 16, 1937 (Box 10)
    - "Forgotten Aspects of Judicial Reforms", Columbia Broadcasting System July 29, 1937 (Box 10)
    - Government Reorganization Bill March 27, 1938 (Box 10)
    - Naval Expansion Bill April 28, 1938 (Box 10)
    - Naval Expansion Bill: Supplementary material (Box 10)
    - Democratic Senatorial Campaign Committee October 1, 1938 (Box 10)
    - "Proposed Reciprocal Taxation of Government Securities," National Broadcasting Company May 15, 1939
      - Speech (Box 10)
      - Correspondence (Box 10)
    - Jefferson Day Speech, Harrisburg, Pennsylvania April 13, 1939 (Box 10)
    - Wisconsin Jefferson Day Address May 6, 1939 (Box 10)
    - Washington College of Law Commencement Address June 9, 1939 (Box 10)
    - "Neutrality"
      - Radio Address October 5, 1939 (Box 10)
      - Supplementary Material, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Maryland Historical Society Address, October 9,1939 (Box 10)
    - Charles A. Lindbergh and Canadian-American Relations October 20, 1939 (Box 10)
    - Jackson Day Dinner, Detroit January 8, 1940 (Box 10)
    - Ontario Section of the Canadian Bar Association January 27, 1940 (Box 10)
    - "Loan to Finland"; American Forum of the Air January 28, 1940 (Box 10)
    - American Jewish Congress, Detroit February 4, 1940, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Speech to Americans of Polish Descent February 4, 1940 (Box 10)
    - "Our Policy in the Finnish-Russian War," National Radio Forum February 26, 1940
      - Speech (Box 10)
      - Correspondence (Box 10)
    - Jefferson Day Speech, Ebensburg, Penns.; Campaign for Senator Joseph Guffey (Box 11)
    - Oakland County Jefferson Club, Pontiac April 18, 1940 (Box 11)
    - City-wide Women's Democratic Club, Baltimore, Maryland April 25, 1940 (Box 11)
    - "The Government's Responsibility"; May 28, 1940 (Box 11)
    - "Tax for Defense"; American Forum of the Air June 2, 1940 (Box 11)
    - Democratic State Convention, Grand Rapids September 23-24, 1940 (Box 11)
    - "Some Federal Tax Problems"; Real Estate Board of Baltimore February 1, 1941 (Box 11)
    - Democratic Spring State Convention, Grand Rapids February 19-20, 1941 (Box 11)
    - Lend Lease Bill February 27, 1941 (Box 11)
    - Jefferson Day Dinner, Detroit March 29, 1941 (Box 11)
    - Speech to B'nai B'rith, Mackinac Island July 4, 1941 (Box 11)
    - Repeal of Sections of the Neutrality Act November 1941 (Box 11)
    - Tribute to Justice Brandeis, Balfour Day Celebration, Detroit November 2, 1941 (Box 11)
    - Price Control Bill, WJR January 1, 1942 (Box 11)
    - Michigan Sportmen's Congress, Detroit January 31, 1942 (Box 11)
    - "Inflation, What Can We Do About It?" March 2, 1942
      - Speech (Box 11)
      - Correspondence (Box 11)
      - Supplementary material (Box 11)
    - Jefferson Day Speech, Pontiac April 9, 1942 (Box 11)
    - "Price Control and Inflation"; National Radio Forum, N.B.C. May 11, 1942 (Box 11)
    - "How Can We Best Curb Inflation?"; American Forum of the Air May 31, 1942 (Box 11)
    - "Price Control" Radio Broadcast, The Blue Network June 1, 1942 (Box 11)
    - Detroit College of Law June 9, 1942 (Box 11)
    - Western Michigan College of Education, Kalamazoo June 13, 1942 (Box 11)
      (phonograph record of speech also available)
    - Price Control Act Amendment, WMAL September 16, 1942 (Box 11)
    - Senate Address September 24, 1942 (Box 11)
    - March of Time Address September 24, 1942 (Box 11)
    - Wage and Price Control Legislation, CBS Radio September 25, 1942 (Box 11)
    - "The Navy's Challenge for Service September 30, 1942 (Box 11)
    - Universal Newsreel Statement October 6, 1942 (Box 11)
    - Campaign speeches September 1942, undated (Box 11)
    - Campaign speeches October 1-20, 1942 (Box 11)
    - Campaign speeches October 21-31, 1942 (Box 11)
    - Campaign speeches November 1942 (Box 11)
    - Campaign speeches 1942 (non-Brown) (Box 11)
    - Office of Price Administration speeches 1943 undated (Box 11)
    - March of Tine January 21, 1943 (Box 11)
    - Washington Reports on Rationing February 14, 1943 (Box 11)
    - Radio speech February 16, 1943 (Box 11)
    - Technical Association of the Pulp and Paper Industry February 18, 1943 (Box 11)
    - CBS Report to the Nation February 21, 1943 (Box 11)
    - Betty Crocker Program February 24, 1943 (Box 11)
    - Message on Black Markets February 26, 1943 (Box 11)
    - CBS "A & P's Food News Roundup" February 26, 1943 (Box 11)
    - WWDC Radio Program: Interview with Esther Van Wagoner Tufty February 27, 1943 (Box 11)
    - WWDC Radio Remarks March 2, 1943 (Box 11)
    - "Consumer Participation in Price Control and Rationing" March 16, 1943 (Box 11)
      (Phonograph record of speech also available)
    - Omaha (Neb.) Chamber of Commerce speech March 17, 1943 (Box 11)
    - American Association of School Administrators March 19, 1943 (Box 11)
    - CBS Broadcast April 3, 1943 (Box 11)
    - Houston Chamber of Commerce April 12, 1943 (Box 11)
    - KTSA, San Antonio Radio Message April 13, 1943 (Box 11)
    - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce April 15, 1943 (Box 11)
    - WOL Radio Message on coal workers strike April 30, 1943 (Box 11)
    - "We the People" Radio Program May 9, 1943 (Box 11)
    - NBC Radio, "War Ration Book Three" May 27, 1943 (Box 11)
    - WRC Radio Speech June 24, 1943 (Box 11)
    - Earl Godwin Radio Program June 28, 1943 (Box 11)
    - Boston Chamber of Commerce July 16, 1943 (Box 11)
    - Boston Chamber of Commerce July 16, 1943 (Box 11)
    - WJR (Detroit) George Cushing Program August 7, 1943 (Box 11)
    - "Home Front Reporter" October 1, 1943 (Box 11)
    - Inland Daily Press Association, Chicago October 13, 1943 (Box 11)
    - Speeches January-September 1944 (Box 11)
    - Speeches October 1944 (Box 11)
    - Speeches November-December 1944 (Box 11)
    - Speeches 1945, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Speeches 1946, 6 folders (Box 12)
    - Speeches 1947, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Speeches 1948 (Box 12)
    - Speeches 1949, 6 folders (Box 12)
    - Speeches 1950 (Box 12)
    - Speeches 1951, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Speech: Newcomen Society, Detroit, "Alex Dow (1862-1942) For 28 Years the President of Detroit Edison" May 8, 1951, 5 folders (Box 12)
    - Speeches 1952 (Box 12)
    - Speeches 1953 (Box 12)
    - Speeches 1954 (Box 12)
    - Speeches 1955 (Box 12)
    - Speeches 1956-1967 (Box 12)
  - Speech Correspondence
    - 1945-1950 (Box 12)
    - 1951 (Box 12)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 12)
    - 1954 (Box 12)
  - Remarks made in U.S. Senate
    - 75th Congress, First Session (Box 12)
    - 75th Congress, Second Session (Box 13)
    - 76th Congress, First Session (Box 13)
    - 76th Congress, Second Session (Box 13)
    - 77th Congress, First and Second Session (Box 13)
    - Requests for corrections in Congressional Record (Box 13)
  - Miscellaneous
    - List of speech invitations (accepted and rejected) 1944-1954 (Box 13)
    - Speeches (non-Brown) (Box 13)
  - Background materials for speeches
    - Automotive Industry (Box 13)
    - CCC (Box 13)
    - Education (Box 13)
    - Labor Disputes (Judge Anderson Case) (Box 13)
    - Cost of World War (Box 13)
    - Cost of Government (Box 13)
    - Crime and Courts (Box 13)
    - Debt Limit (Box 13)
    - Lend-Lease Bill Debate (Box 13)
    - OPA, 3 folders (Box 13)
    - Miscellaneous, 5 folders (Box 13)
- Office of Price Administration files 1943, 0.5 linear feet
  The Office of Price Administration series (0.5 linear ft.; 1943) is small and consists largely of personal materials, such as speeches, scrapbooks, and congratulatory letters. The official records of the OPA are located in the National Archives in Washington.
  - Regional Administrators meeting April 1943 (Box 13)
  - Bohn Aluminum & Brass Corporation fraud case 1943 (Box 13)
  - Dairy Industry Committee 1943 (Box 13)
  - Statement urging purchase of war bonds 1943 (Box 13)
  - Miscellaneous Price Material (Box 13)
  - Resignation and final report October 19, 1943 (Box 13)
  - Letters of Congratulations (sample) upon appointment as OPA Administrator 1943, 4 folders (Box 13)
  - Appointment book January-October 1943 (Box 13)
  - Published government document material, 11 items (Box 13)
- Topical Files 1936-1968, 1 linear feet
  The Topical files series (1 linear ft.; 1936-1968) relates to Brown's varied historical and academic interests, such as his involvement with the Michigan Civil War Centennial Observance Commission, the Michigan Historical Commission, and Albion College. Information about his travels are included here.
  - Historical Interests and Activities
    - Michigan Civil War Centennial Observance Commission 1960-1966, 8 folders (Box 14)
    - Papers concerning review of "Furs By Astor" 1964 (Box 14)
    - Papers concerning anchor salvaged near Bois Blanc Island 1957-1958 (Box 14)
    - Papers concerning proposed discontinuance of rail car ferry service at Mackinac 1963-1964 (Box 14)
    - Michigan Historical Commission 1952-1965, 13 folders (Box 14)
    - Miscellaneous Historical Interests, 4 folders (Box 14)
  - Other interests and topics
    - Papers concerning review of "Philadelphia Lawyer" 1945-1946 (Box 14)
    - Papers concerning proposed Arthur H. Vandenberg Memorial Lecture Series in International Relations at Wayne University 1951 (Box 14)
    - Papers concerning Federal Power Commission appointment and gas shortage situation 1948 (Box 14)
    - Michigan State Office Buildings Corporation 1950-1954, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Papers concerning the Renegotiation Act and Michigan iron ore resources 1951 (Box 14)
    - Harbors (Box 14)
    - Frank Murphy Memorial 1949-1954 (Box 14)
    - Albion College, 3 folders (Box 14)
    - Trip to Japan 1968, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Businessmen's Committee for Seasoned Management (Montgomery Ward-Wolfson Proxy Dispute) 1955, 3 folders (Box 14)
    - Henry A. Wallace papers 1942 (Box 14)
    - Washington House miscellanea 1936-1940 (Box 14)
- Business and legal files 1902-1973, 8 linear feet
  A significant part of the collection documents Brown's business and legal interests. Business and legal files (8 linear ft.; 1902-1973) is especially valuable for information on Brown's banking interests and his involvement with St. Ignace and Mackinac Island land development. For the historian of the Mackinac Straits, these files detail the operation of the Arnold Transit Company, the firm which operated the ferry between Mackinaw City and St. Ignace, and to Mackinac Island. Brown was for many years a member of the board of directors of the Arnold Company.
  - James J. Brown law firm, later Brown and Brown Law Firm
    - Letter book 1902-1904 of James J. Brown law firm; later letterbook, January-August 1917 of Brown and Brown Law Firm (Box 15)
    - Letter book August 1917-March 1918 (Box 15)
    - Letter book March 1919-March 1920 (Box 15)
    - Letter book March-December 1920 (Box 15)
    - Correspondence 1913-1920 (Box 16)
    - Wills drawn up 1915-1928, 3 folders (Box 16)
    - Mackinac Island State Park Commission vs. David W. Murray (argument over the ownership of Mackinac Island Beach Front), 8 folders (Box 16)
    - Papers concerning legal work for Charles Hessel circa 1912-1928, 3 folders (Box 16)
    - Papers concerning Charles Hessel Estate 1940-1943 (Box 16)
    - Irving Berlin, Inc. and Mrs. R. Van Allen Webster 1925 (Box 16)
    - Papers concerning legal work for the Murray family 1926-1928, 5 folders (Box 16)
    - Papers concerning legal work for William St. James 1927-1929, 4 folders (Box 16)
    - Papers concerning legal work for the St. Ignace First National Bank on the matter of St. Ignace State Ferry Dock Property 1931-1934, 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Estate of David Murray 1934, 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Estate of Rose Van Allen Webster 1935-1944, 8 folders (Box 16)
  - Financial materials
    - Financial data cards (Box 17)
    - Monthly financial statements 1933, 1936, 1939 (fragmentary) (Box 17)
    - Monthly financial statements 1940-1965, 26 folders (Box 17)
    - Legal miscellanea, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Various business interests
    - Maps of business related properties, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - St. Ignace office correspondence 1937-1943, 5 folders (Box 17)
    - Requests for contributions to charitable and other organizations (Box 17)
    - Petoskey Cement Company (Box 17)
    - Twin City Packing Company (Box 17)
    - Asam Motor Company
      - 1940-1942 (Box 17)
      - Supplementary material (Box 17)
    - State Board of Law Examiners miscellanea (Box 17)
    - Sault Ste. Marie First National Bank (Box 18)
    - Federated Publications 1937-1939 (Box 18)
    - Federated Publications 1940 (Box 18)
    - Federated Publications 1941-1942 (Box 18)
    - National Bank of Detroit-loan correspondence (Box 18)
    - National Bank of Detroit-miscellanea (Box 18)
    - St. Ignace First National Bank 1933-1935 (Box 18)
    - St. Ignace First National Bank 1936-1937 (Box 18)
    - St. Ignace First National Bank 1938-1942 (Box 18)
    - St. Ignace First National Bank circa 1945-1965 (Box 18)
    - St. Ignace First National Bank circa 1945-1965 (Box 18)
    - St. Ignace First National Bank: Annual Reports (Box 18)
    - Birmingham National Bank (Box 18)
    - National Bank of Bay City (Box 18)
    - Charlevoix County Bank (Box 18)
    - First National Bank of Detroit 1935-September 1942, 15 folders (Box 18)
    - National Bank of Detroit miscellanea, 3 folders (Box 18)
    - Cheboygan Citizens National Bank, 2 folders (Box 18)
    - Michigan National Bank (Box 18)
    - Farmers and Manufacturers Beet Sugar Association (Box 19)
    - Great Lakes Sugar Company, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Lamborn Sugar Company (Box 19)
    - Paulding Sugar Company
      - 1932-1943, 6 folders (Box 19)
      - Tax Case (Box 19)
      - Miscellanea, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Union Lumber Company, 4 folders (Box 19)
    - Dunham Company (Box 19)
    - Arthur A. Schupp (Box 19)
    - Papers concerning Lake Superior Iron Ore 1947-1951, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Bills paid (Box 19)
    - Papers concerning gift tax problem 1935-1964 (Box 19)
    - Income tax material 1933-1942 (Box 19)
    - Income tax material 1945-1948 (Box 19)
    - Income tax material 1949-1950 (Box 19)
    - Income tax material 1951-1952 (Box 19)
    - Income tax material 1953-1954 (Box 19)
    - Family financial papers, 3 folders (Box 19)
  - Arnold Transit Company files
    - 1921-1942, 36 folders (Box 20)
    - 1943-1973, 31 folders (Box 21)
    - Annual reports 1939-1952 (incomplete) (Box 21)
    - Annual reports 1953-1957 (Box 21)
    - Annual reports 1958-1963 (Box 21)
    - Annual reports 1964-1971 (Box 21)
    - Forms (Box 21)
    - Mackinac Land Company papers 1926-1931, 4 folders (Box 22)
    - Susan Arnold Estate accounts, 7 folders (Box 22)
    - Mackinac Island Hotel Company
      - 1921-1930, 8 folders (Box 22)
      - Reorganization 1930-1934, 11 folders (Box 22)
    - Straits Transit, Inc. vs. Union Terminal Piers, et al. 1964-1967, 4 folders (Box 22)
    - People vs. Tellefson (question of operating automobiles on Mackinac Island) 1935-1936 (Box 22)
    - Chicago, Duluth and Georgian Bay Transit Co. vs. city of Mackinac Island 1941-1942, 3 folders (Box 22)
    - Laura M. Gonser vs. city of Mackinac Island 1942-1955 (Box 22)
- Scrapbooks and clippings 1933-1954, 5 linear feet
  The Scrapbooks and Clippings (5 linear ft.; 1933-1954) series consists of thirty-seven scrapbooks and several folders of loose clippings. Composed mainly of clippings, many of the volumes also include programs and scattered photographs. The scrapbooks are mainly from the period when Brown was in the U.S. Congress.
  - Scrapbooks March 1933-July 1937, 15 volumes (Box 23)
  - Scrapbooks July 1937-June 1940, 5 volumes (Box 24)
  - Scrapbooks June 1940-August 1942, 5 volumes (Box 25)
  - Scrapbooks August 1942-August 1943, 6 volumes (Box 26)
  - Scrapbooks August 1943-1949, 2 volumes (Box 27)
  - Scrapbook concerning Mackinac Bridge activities 1953-February 1954, 1 volumes (Box 27)
  - Scrapbook containing programs, photographs and clippings 1938-1950, 1 volumes (Box 27)
  - Scrapbook containing letters of congratulations upon appointment as chairman of Detroit Edison 1944 (Box 27)
  - Scrapbook containing newspaper obituaries and letters of condolence (Box 27)
  - Newspaper clippings concerning Mackinac Bridge Dedication, 3 folders (Box 28)
  - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings, 4 folders (Box 28)
- Visual Materials